<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://stonemcyt.github.io/susFic/blog</id>
    <title>susFic Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-08-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://stonemcyt.github.io/susFic/blog"/>
    <subtitle>susFic Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://stonemcyt.github.io/susFic/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Year 0 Chapter Two: Meeting the Princess]]></title>
        <id>https://stonemcyt.github.io/susFic/blog/chapter-two-meeting-the-princess</id>
        <link href="https://stonemcyt.github.io/susFic/blog/chapter-two-meeting-the-princess"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Date: 2nd Januay Year 0]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="theme-admonition theme-admonition-info alert alert--info admonition_LlT9"><div class="admonitionHeading_tbUL"><span class="admonitionIcon_kALy"><svg viewBox="0 0 14 16"><path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M7 2.3c3.14 0 5.7 2.56 5.7 5.7s-2.56 5.7-5.7 5.7A5.71 5.71 0 0 1 1.3 8c0-3.14 2.56-5.7 5.7-5.7zM7 1C3.14 1 0 4.14 0 8s3.14 7 7 7 7-3.14 7-7-3.14-7-7-7zm1 3H6v5h2V4zm0 6H6v2h2v-2z"></path></svg></span>info</div><div class="admonitionContent_S0QG"><p>Date: 2nd Januay Year 0</p></div></div><p>Dammit I cursed to myself my legs are screaming whilst the guards chased after me. Legs screaming, breath panting, hooves screaming. I overhear screams and shouts of various military orders and vaguely catch a name. Merloy? No Merlin. Thats right Merlin a unicorn with a beautiful white coat with grey streaks like a zebra led the chase in tight a V formation. Legs tiring, I jumped up into the air with putting a lot of trust into my wings to fly up. </p><p>"YES, I'M FLYING!" I screamed out for the world to see.</p><p>Dammit, seconds later I was tackled into the ground with Merlin holding me down with the guards rushing over to cuff me. The hay I have done nothing wrong. The orange one knocked me in the head, and all went dark.</p><p><strong> Hours Later: </strong></p><p>I wake up cold, tired, and hungry but comfortable. My senses start to return, hoof on my pounding head I look around and get used to my surroundings. A closed double door with gold knobs, fancy glass painted windows and a 4-poster bed. I look to my left and jump up a purple pony with a darn beautiful mane stare at me. My eyes refocused and realised she has unicorn horn and wings. My mouth agape she tilts her head, looks at me, and starts to speak, her voice like a thousand angels.</p><p>"Hello! I am Twilight Sparkle welcome to Equestria!" Said the purple unicorn-Pegasus pony.
"Ummm, Hi I'm Snek," I calmy replied.
"Sorry about your head, flash wasn’t meant to hit you that hard. Just enough so you would stop running away" Twilight calmy said.</p><p>Twilight's horn started to glow, and my headache started to fade.</p><p>"Better" the unicorn-Pegasus inquired.</p><p>"Indeed, thank you" I bowed whilst sitting down. Awkward ey?</p><p>The noise of knocking doors jerk us out of the awkward silence. The doors creaked opened, two ponies on each side with Flash in the middle he glared intensely at me. What I could only assume is jealousy. </p><p>His deep booming voice ricocheted across the room, "Guards cuff him”.</p><p>The guards rush up towards the bed with some magical handful thingies in hand, but twilight stands between them, "That will not be necessary, Snek won't cause any harm to the palace or me". I awkward nod. The orange idiot opens his mouth, "But love-". Twilight holds a hoof out to him and interrupts him mid-sentence "it will be fine".</p><p>The orange balloon huffed and glared at me before instructing the guards to escort me up to the throne room leaving Twilight behind. I was escorted upwards throw the twisting halls with beautiful red carpets past portraits of what I could only assume are the princesses. I enter this grand room which has giant glass windows that overlooked the buildings bellow. 4 Thrones sat in the room with four guards on each side. A second later all four thrones where filled. Twilight on the left, followed by some white, green hair one on her right, a dark blue princess with a nice flowing mane and a little grey Pegasus on the right with a muffin.</p><p>The white coloured one opened her mouth but no words game out it was like she was speaking in my head "Hello Snek, welcome to Equestria on my left sites Princess Luna and on her left sits Derpy Princess of Greece”.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Snek</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/StoneMcYT</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="year0" term="year0"/>
        <category label="snek" term="snek"/>
        <category label="twlight" term="twlight"/>
        <category label="luna" term="luna"/>
        <category label="celestia" term="celestia"/>
        <category label="royal-guards" term="royal-guards"/>
        <category label="merlin" term="merlin"/>
        <category label="sfw" term="sfw"/>
        <category label="pov" term="pov"/>
        <category label="capitol" term="capitol"/>
        <category label="castle" term="castle"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Year 0 Chapter One: New Beginnings]]></title>
        <id>https://stonemcyt.github.io/susFic/blog/chapter-one-new-beginnings</id>
        <link href="https://stonemcyt.github.io/susFic/blog/chapter-one-new-beginnings"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an early chapter one draft so we can publish the webpage early and get everyone on the same system. This chapter will NOT be extended in terms of content but grammer/spelling/style will be revamped.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="theme-admonition theme-admonition-info alert alert--info admonition_LlT9"><div class="admonitionHeading_tbUL"><span class="admonitionIcon_kALy"><svg viewBox="0 0 14 16"><path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M7 2.3c3.14 0 5.7 2.56 5.7 5.7s-2.56 5.7-5.7 5.7A5.71 5.71 0 0 1 1.3 8c0-3.14 2.56-5.7 5.7-5.7zM7 1C3.14 1 0 4.14 0 8s3.14 7 7 7 7-3.14 7-7-3.14-7-7-7zm1 3H6v5h2V4zm0 6H6v2h2v-2z"></path></svg></span>info</div><div class="admonitionContent_S0QG"><p>This is an early chapter one draft so we can publish the webpage early and get everyone on the same system. This chapter will NOT be extended in terms of content but grammer/spelling/style will be revamped.</p></div></div><p>It was one dark morning where I woke up in some unkown cave with a bright shining glowing orb in the center. I rubbed my eyes and walked straight into the glowing light unsure of where it lead to or even why I walked towards it. Stepping through that portal I became a pony not just any random pony, a bright blue technicolor pony standing in the middle of a busy street, I looked at myself looked behind, underneeth and behind again. Damn I've got wings now.</p><p>When I finally stop glazing and trying to flap my wings I was amazed by my suroundings. So many beautiful farm houses with other ponies walking around it was like an explosin of all pony sensnes. Then I realised, oh buck. I'm small  I'm a foal. A young young young foal. I stood up and galoped on the cobblestone streets to the outskirts of the city. I needed someplace to think as well as rest to figure out what the hay this world is and what am I doing here.</p><p>I rode off into the distance, the scenery started changing from houses to farms and finally to large open planes with flowing hills. I found a patch of grass under a beautiful tree and sat down. Moments later a squad of what looks like 4 peagsus ponies in golden armor entered the horizon, I paniked and fled running as fast as I can but they chassed after me.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Snek</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/StoneMcYT</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="year0" term="year0"/>
        <category label="Snek" term="Snek"/>
        <category label="SFW" term="SFW"/>
        <category label="Pov" term="Pov"/>
        <category label="USA" term="USA"/>
    </entry>
</feed>